Guide to the African American Television Scripts
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
African American television scripts
1950-1994
JWJ MSS 90
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
18.14
(44 boxes)
The collection consists of scripts and a small number of photographs documenting approximately eighty-five television programs featuring African American actors, entertainers, and topics from the 1950s through the 1990s. While some material from an earlier period of television broadcasting is present, including Amos and Andy (1952), Buelah (1950-1953), and The Jack Benny Show (1964), scripts for shows that aired in the 1970s and 1980s predominate. Sanford and Son (1974-1976), The Jeffersons (1975-1978), Good Times (1974-1976) and The Cosby Show (1984-1991), situation comedies depicting African American familes in varying social conditions, are particularly well represented. In addition to long-running programs, the collection includes scripts for variety specials, miniseries, and pilots such as Guess Who's Coming to Dinner (1975) and Skin Game (1974). The collection also includes a file documenting the Association of Black Motion Picture and Television Producers, including meeting minutes and copies of outgoing correspondence.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Purchased from George Robert Minkoff Inc. on the Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection Fund, 1999.
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by program title.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of scripts and a small number of photographs documenting approximately eighty-five television programs featuring African American actors, entertainers, and topics from the 1950s through the 1990s. While some material from an earlier period of television broadcasting is present, including Amos and Andy (1952), Buelah (1950-1953), and The Jack Benny Show (1964), scripts for shows that aired in the 1970s and 1980s predominate. Sanford and Son (1974-1976), The Jeffersons (1975-1978), Good Times (1974-1976) and The Cosby Show (1984-1991), situation comedies depicting African American familes in varying social conditions, are particularly well represented. In addition to long-running programs, the collection includes scripts for variety specials, miniseries, and pilots such as Guess Who's Coming to Dinner (1975) and Skin Game (1974). The collection also includes a file documenting the Association of Black Motion Picture and Television Producers, including meeting minutes and copies of outgoing correspondence.
African American entertainers; African Americans in television broadcasting; African Americans on television; Blacks in television broadcasting -- United States; Blacks on television -- United States; Popular culture -- United States; Television -- United States; Television broadcasting -- United States; Television programs -- United States; Television scripts; United States -- Race relations -- Drama; United States -- Social conditions -- Drama; Television scripts
- African American Television Scripts, (44 boxes)
  - 227
    - "Pick Six", 1986 (Box 1)
    - "Slam Dunked", 1986 (Box 1)
  - All in the Family
    - "George and Archie Make A Deal", 1974 (Box 1)
  - Amos 'n' Andy
    - "The Income Tax Show", 1952 (Box 1)
    - Photographs, undated; 2 (Box 1)
  - The A-Team
    - Untitled original pilot, 1982 (Box 1)
    - "Beneath The Surface", 1986 (Box 1)
    - "Family Reunion", 1986 (Box 1)
    - "The Grey Team", 1986 (Box 1)
    - "Play It Again, Murdock", 1986 (Box 1)
    - "Point Of No Return", 1986 (Box 1)
  - Amen
    - "The Courtship Of Bess Harper", undated (Box 2)
  - Association of Black Motion Picture and Television Producers
    - Constitution, network liaisons, correspondence, and minutes of meetings, 1983 (Box 2)
  - B.A.D. Cats
    - Untitled pilot, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Revised first draft, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Revised second draft, 1979 (Box 2)
    - Revised shooting script, 1979 (Box 2)
    - "The Bel Air Bandit", 1980 (Box 2)
    - "Death Car", 1980 (Box 2)
    - "Death Car" (final draft), 1980 (Box 2)
    - "Die, Cheerleader, Die", 1980 (Box 2)
    - "Die, Cheerleader, Die" (final script), 1980 (Box 2)
    - "Let's Put Sam Away", 1979 (Box 3)
    - "Let's Put Sam Away" (final script), 1980 (Box 3)
    - "The Rolling Bordello", 1979 (Box 3)
    - "The Rolling Bordello" (shooting script), 1980 (Box 3)
    - "Semi-Paradise" (final shooting script), 1979 (Box 3)
    - "Snatched", 1979 (Box 3)
  - Barefoot In The Park
    - "The Bed", 1968 (Box 3)
    - "In Sickness and in Health", undated (Box 3)
  - Baretta
    - "The Inside Man", 1976 (Box 3)
    - "And Down Will Come Baby", 1976 (Box 3)
    - "The Dippers", 1975 (Box 3)
    - "The Mojo Man", 1976 (Box 3)
    - "The Good Bye Orphan Annie Blues", 1975 (Box 3)
  - Barney Miller
    - Untitled pilot, 1974 (Box 4)
    - "Ambush", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "The Guest", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "Hair", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "The Horse Thief", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "The Lay-Off", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "Werewolf", 1976 (Box 4)
    - "Snow Job", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "You Dirty Rat", 1975 (Box 4)
  - Battlestar Galactica
    - "The Young Warriors", 1978 (Box 4)
  - Beulah
    - Photographs, 1950-1953 (Box 4)
  - Brian's Song
    - Final draft, 1971 (Box 4)
  - The Carol Burnett Show
    - "Sammy Davies Jr.", 1975 (Box 4)
    - "The Pointer Sisters", 1975 (Box 4)
  - Checking In
    - "Florence And The Salesman", 1981 (Box 5)
      Related Archival Materials note
      See also: Facts of Life
  - Cher
    - "Jimmy Walker", 1975 (Box 5)
    - "The Pointer Sisters and Redd Fox", 1975 (Box 5)
  - Clifton Davis Special
    - First draft, 1976 (Box 5)
    - Second draft, 1976 (Box 5)
  - Coast Productions Incorporated
    - "History of a Minority Owned Production Company", 1976 (Box 5)
  - The Cop And The Kid
    - Untitled pilot, 1974 (Box 5)
    - Untitled pilot, third draft, 1975 (Box 5)
    - "The Ballad Of Joe", 1976 (Box 5)
    - "The Ballad Of Joe" (final draft), 1975 (Box 5)
    - "Danger, Men Working", 1976 (Box 5)
    - "Daydream", 1975 (Box 5)
    - "Happy Birthday, Champ", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "The Hero", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "The Hero" (final draft), 1975 (Box 6)
    - "The Hero" (revised final draft), 1975 (Box 6)
    - "A Little Understanding Goes A Short Way", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "A Little Understanding Goes A Short Way" (final draft), 1975 (Box 6)
    - "Notre Dame By 50", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "Not With My Teacher", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "Previous Engagement", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "The Weekend Guest", 1975 (Box 6)
    - "You'll Look Great In Basic Black", 1975 (Box 6)
  - The Cosby Show
    - "Auction", 1985 (Box 6)
    - "Bonjour, Sondra", 1984 (Box 6)
    - "Bring Me The Lip Gloss Of Deirdre Arpelle", 1991 (Box 6)
    - "Clair's Sister", 1985 (Box 6)
    - "Clair's Sister" (final draft), 1985 (Box 6)
    - "Clair's Toe", 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Cliff In Love", 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Cliff In Love" (final draft), 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Cliff's Birthday", 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Cliff's Birthday" (final draft), 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Close To Home", 1986 (Box 7)
    - "The Day The Spores Landed", 1989 (Box 7)
    - "Denise Drives", 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Denise Drives" (revised first draft), 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Denise Drives" (final draft), 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Denise's Decision", 1986 (Box 7)
    - "Denise's Decision" (final draft), 1986 (Box 7)
    - "Denise's Friend", 1985 (Box 7)
    - "Denise's Friend" (revised first draft), 1985 (Box 7)
    - "The Dentist", 1986 (Box 8)
    - "First Day Of School", 1985 (Box 8)
    - "First Day Of School" (final draft), 1985 (Box 8)
    - "First Day Of School" (revised final draft), 1985 (Box 8)
    - "For Men Only", 1991 (Box 8)
    - "The Getaway", 1991 (Box 8)
    - "Halloween", 1985 (Box 8)
    - "Halloween" (final draft), 1985 (Box 8)
    - "Happy Anniversary", 1985 (Box 8)
    - "Happy Anniversary" (revised first draft), 1985 (Box 8)
    - "Happy Anniversary" (final draft), 1985 (Box 8)
    - "How Ugly Is He?", 1984 (Box 8)
    - "How Ugly Is He?" (final draft), 1984 (Box 8)
    - "The Juicer", 1985 (Box 9)
    - "The Juicer" (revised first draft), 1985 (Box 9)
    - "The Juicer" (final draft), 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Mrs. Westlake", 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Off To the Races", 1986 (Box 9)
    - "Physician Of The Year", 1984 (Box 9)
    - "Play It Again Russell", 1986 (Box 9)
    - "Rudy's Sick", 1984 (Box 9)
    - "Rudy Suits Up", 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Rudy Suits Up" (final draft), 1985 (Box 9)
    - "The Slumber Party", 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Theo And Cockroach", 1986 (Box 9)
    - "Theo And The Older Woman", 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Theo And The Older Woman" (revised first draft), 1985 (Box 9)
    - "Theo And The Older Woman" (final draft), 1985 (Box 10)
    - "Theo's Future", 1991 (Box 10)
    - "Theo's Holiday", 1986 (Box 10)
    - "Theo's Holiday" (final draft), 1986 (Box 10)
    - "A Touch Of Wonder", 1986 (Box 10)
    - "A Touch Of Wonder", 1986 (Box 10)
    - "Vanessa's New Class", 1985 (Box 10)
    - "The Younger Woman", 1985 (Box 10)
  - Daktari
    - "Born To Die", 1966 (Box 10)
    - "Deadline To Kill", 1966 (Box 10)
    - "The Return Of Clarence", 1966 (Box 10)
  - Daniel Boone
    - "A Bearskin For Jamie Blue", 1969 (Box 10)
  - The Diahann Carroll Show
    - "Show #1, George Benson", 1976 (Box 10)
    - "Show #4, Sammy Davies Jr.", 1976 (Box 10)
  - Diana!
    - Musical special starring Diana Ross, 1970 (Box 11)
  - Diff'rent Strokes
    - "Getting Involved", 1979 (Box 11)
    - "The Hero", 1979 (Box 11)
    - "The Job", 1979 (Box 11)
    - "The Trip", 1979 (Box 11)
    - "Son Of Crossover", 1979 (Box 11)
  - Dinah and Her New Best Friends
    - Lola Falana, 1976 (Box 11)
  - Dynasty
    - "The Birthday", 1986 (Box 11)
    - "The Birthday" (final draft), 1986 (Box 11)
  - Enos
    - First episode, untitled, 1980 (Box 11)
    - First episode, final draft, 1980 (Box 11)
    - "Blue Flu", 1980 (Box 11)
    - "Grits And Green Strike Again", 1980 (Box 11)
    - "Grits And Green strike Again" (final draft), 1980 (Box 11)
    - "Horse Cops", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "The Hostage", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "The House Cleaners", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "The Mandarin Shakedown", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "One Daisy Per Summer", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "Snowjob", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "Snowjob" (revised final draft), 1980 (Box 12)
    - "Where's The Corpus", 1980 (Box 12)
    - "Where's The Corpus" (second draft), 1980 (Box 12)
  - An Evening With Julie Andrews and Harry Belafonte
    - Script, 1969 (Box 12)
  - The Facts Of Life
    See also: Checking In
    - "E. G. O. C.", 1984 (Box 12)
    - "The Last Drive-In", 1985 (Box 12)
    - "Teacher, Teacher", 1985 (Box 12)
  - Fame
    - "Gonna Learn How To Fly", 1983 (Box 13)
    - "Pros and Cons", 1986 (Box 13)
  - Flip Wilson...of course
    - First draft, 1974 (Box 13)
  - Flip Wilson Special
    - Second draft, 1974 (Box 13)
    - First draft, 1975 (Box 13)
    - Final draft, 1975 (Box 13)
    - First draft, 1975 (Box 13)
  - The Fresh Prince Of Bel-Air
    - "All Guts No Glory", 1993 (Box 13)
    - "Blood Is Thicker Than Mud", 1993 (Box 13)
    - "Father Of The Year", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "Fresh Prince After Dark", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "Hex And The Single Guy", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "Hilary Gets A Life", 1991 (Box 14)
    - "Home Is Where the Heart Attack Is ", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "I Know Why The Caged Bird Screams", 1994 (Box 14)
    - "It's Better To Have Loved And Lost It", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "The Philadelphia Story", 1994 (Box 14)
    - "Take My Cousin Please", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "When You Hit Upon A Star", 1994 (Box 14)
    - "Who's The Boss", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "Will Goes A Courtin", 1993 (Box 14)
    - "You've Got To Be A Football Hero", 1993 (Box 14)
  - Get Christie Love
    - "The Big Rematch", 1975 (Box 15)
    - "The Big Rematch"(revised draft), 1975 (Box 15)
    - "Bullet From The Grave", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Deadly Betrayal", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Deadly Betrayal" (revised draft), 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Deadly Justice", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "The Deadly Sport", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Death On Delivery", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Downbeat For A Dead Man", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Emperor On Death Street", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "Fatal Image", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "A Few Excess People", 1975 (Box 15)
    - "For The Family Honor", 1974 (Box 15)
    - "From Paris With Love", 1975 (Box 15)
    - "A High Fashion Heist", 1975 (Box 16)
    - "A Highway To Murder", 1974 (Box 16)
    - "I'm Your New Neighbor", 1975 (Box 16)
    - "The Longest Fall", 1974 (Box 16)
    - "Market For Murder", 1975 (Box 16)
    - "Murder On High C.", 1975 (Box 16)
    - "My Son The Murderer", 1977 (Box 16)
    - "Our Lady In London", 1974 (Box 16)
    - "Our Lady In London" (revised draft), 1974 (Box 16)
    - "Pawn Ticket for Murder", 1974 (Box 16)
    - "To Many Games In Town", 1974 (Box 16)
  - Gladys Knight and the Pips
    - Tape #2, 1975 (Box 16)
    - Tape #3, 1975 (Box 16)
  - Good Times
    - "The Baby", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "The Breakup", 1976 (Box 17)
    - "Cleatus", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "Crosstown Buses Run All Day, Doodah, Doodah", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "The Debutante Ball", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "The Encyclopedia Hustle", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "The Enlistment", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "Family Business", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "The Family Gun", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "Florida Flips", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "Florida Goes To School", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "Florida The Matchmaker", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "Florida The Woman", 1976 (Box 17)
    - "Florida's Big Gig", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "Florida's Protest", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "Florida's Rich Cousin", 1975 (Box 17)
    - "The Gang", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "The Gang Part Two", 1974 (Box 17)
    - "The I.Q. Test", 1974 (Box 18)
    - "The Investigation", 1976 (Box 18)
    - "J.J. Becomes A Man" (part one), 1974 (Box 18)
    - "J.J. Becomes A Man" (part two), 1974 (Box 18)
    - "J.J. In Trouble", 1976 (Box 18)
    - "J.J.'s Fiancee" (part one), 1975 (Box 18)
    - "J.J.'s Fiancee" (part two), 1975 (Box 18)
    - "A Loss of Confidence", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "Love In The Ghetto", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "The Lunch Money Ripoff", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "The Man I Most Admire", 1974 (Box 18)
    - "Michael's Big Fall", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "The Mural", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "My Girl Henrietta", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "The Nude", 1974 (Box 18)
    - "Operation Florida", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "A Place To Die", 1975 (Box 18)
    - "The Politicians", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "The Politicians" (final draft), 1975 (Box 19)
    - "Sometimes There Is No Bottom in the Bottle", 1974 (Box 19)
    - "Sweet Daddy Williams", 1976 (Box 19)
    - "Thelma's Scholarship", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "Thelma's Young Man", 1974 (Box 19)
    - "The Weekend", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "Willona's Dilemma", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "The Windfall", 1974 (Box 19)
  - Grady
    - "Be it Ever So Humble", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "Bureaucracy", 1976 (Box 19)
    - "The Driving Force", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "Grady Takes A Wife", 1976 (Box 19)
    - "Grady's Night In", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "Merry Birthday, Happy Christmas", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "The Meterman", 1975 (Box 19)
    - "The Strike", 1976 (Box 19)
    - "The Weekend", 1975 (Box 19)
  - Guess Who's Coming To Dinner
    - "The Folks" (first draft), 1975 (Box 20)
    - "The Folks" (second draft), 1975 (Box 20)
    - "The Folks" (third draft), 1975 (Box 20)
    - "The Folks" (final draft), 1975 (Box 20)
  - Gus Brown and Midnight Brewster
    - Revised shooting script, 1984 (Box 20)
  - H. Andrew Williams Kaleidoscope
    - Final draft, 1968 (Box 20)
  - Head Of The Class
    - "Crimes of the Heart", 1987 (Box 20)
    - "Love at First Byte", 1986 (Box 20)
    - "The Outsider", 1986 (Box 20)
    - "Rebel Without A Class", 1986 (Box 20)
    - "The Russians Are Coming, The Russians Are Coming", 1987 (Box 20)
    - "Valentines Day", 1987 (Box 21)
    - "Video Activity", 1987 (Box 21)
    - "Volleyball Anyone?", 1986 (Box 21)
    - "The Way We Weren't", 1986 (Box 21)
    - "You've Got A Friend", 1986 (Box 21)
    - "You've Got A Friend" (final draft), 1986 (Box 21)
  - Hill Street Blues
    - "Little Boil Blue", 1982 (Box 21)
  - Home Is The Hunter
    - Screenplay, 1976 (Box 21)
  - Hot L Baltimore
    - "The Date", 1975 (Box 21)
    - "The Deportation Of Suzy", 1975 (Box 21)
    - "Millie's Beau", 1974 (Box 21)
    - "Mrs. Bellotti's Boyfriend", 1975 (Box 21)
    - "Suzy's Problems", 1975 (Box 21)
  - I Spy
    - "The Seventh Captain", 1967 (Box 21)
    - "Red Sash Of Courage", 1967 (Box 21)
  - In The Heat Of The Night
    - "Trundel's Will Be Done", 1991 (Box 22)
  - The Insiders
    - "Fashion Flame", 1985 (Box 22)
  - Ironside
    - "The 17 Million Dollar Heist", 1974 (Box 22)
    - "All Week Is Sunday", 1973 (Box 22)
    - "Backfire", 1970 (Box 22)
    - "Murder By The Book", 1973 (Box 22)
    - "Ordeal", 1974 (Box 22)
    - "Ordeal By Terror", 1974 (Box 22)
    - "Stunts Unlimited", 1974 (Box 22)
    - "This Could Blow Your Mind", 1970 (Box 22)
    - "Too Many Victims", 1970 (Box 22)
    - "Two Sides To Every Coin", 1973 (Box 23)
    - "The Walls a Tumbling Down", 1974 (Box 23)
    - "The Walls a Tumbling Down" (revised final), 1974 (Box 23)
  - The Jack Benny Television Program
    - The Cat Burgler, 1964 (Box 23)
  - The Jackson Family
    - Shows 1-4, 1976 (Box 23)
  - The Jeffersons
    - "The Break Up" (part one), 1975 (Box 23)
    - "The Break Up" (part two), 1975 (Box 23)
    - "A Dinner For Harry", 1975 (Box 23)
    - "Florence's Problem", 1975 (Box 23)
    - "Former Neighbors", 1975 (Box 23)
    - "George and the Manager", 1975 (Box 23)
    - "George Meets Whittendale", 1976 (Box 23)
    - "George's Alibi", 1975 (Box 23)
    - "George's Best Friend", 1975 (Box 23)
    - "George's Family Tree", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "George's First Vacation", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "George Won't Talk", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Harry and Daphne", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Jefferson Vs. Jefferson", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Jenny's Grandparents", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Jenny's Low", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Lionel Cries Uncle", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Lionel The Playboy", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Louise Feels Useless", 1974 (Box 24)
    - "Louise's Award", 1978 (Box 24)
    - "Louise's Cookbook", 1976 (Box 24)
    - "Louise's Daughter", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Lunch With Mama", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Meet The Press", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Mr. Piano Man", 1975 (Box 24)
    - "Mother Jefferson's Birthday", 1976 (Box 24)
    - "Mother Jefferson's Fall", 1975 (Box 25)
    - "Movin' On Down", 1975 (Box 25)
    - "Rich Man's Disease", 1975 (Box 25)
    - "Tennis, Anyone?", 1976 (Box 25)
    - "Uncle Bertram", 1975 (Box 25)
    - "The Wedding", 1976 (Box 25)
  - Julia
    - "The Eve Of Adam", 1969 (Box 25)
    - "You Can't Beat Drums", 1969 (Box 25)
  - King
    - Script, undated; 2 (Box 25)
  - Kings of the Hill (aired as Palmerstown)
    - "The Black Travelers", 1980 (Box 25)
    - "The Black Travelers II", 1980 (Box 25)
    - "Kidnapped", 1979 (Box 26)
  - L. A. Law
    - "Canon Of Ethics", 1987 (Box 26)
    - "Hand Roll Express", 1987 (Box 26)
    - "Fetus Completus", 1988 (Box 26)
  - Law and Order
    - "Blood Is Thicker..", 1991 (Box 26)
    - "His Hour Upon The Stage", 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Severance", 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Severance" (revised draft), 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Star Struck", 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Star Struck" (revised draft), 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Trust", 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Trust" (revised draft), 1991 (Box 26)
    - "Trust" (revised draft), 1991 (Box 27)
    - "Vengeance", 1991 (Box 27)
    - "Vengeance" (revised draft), 1991 (Box 27)
  - Lena
    - Screenplay, 1979 (Box 27)
      Scope and Contents
      Accompanied by letter from Jacques Wilson to George E. Crosby.
  - Lola Folana
    Redd Foxx as guest star.
    - Final draft, 1976 (Box 27)
  - The Love Boat
    Scripts are identified by production code numbers.
    - K-87 (13), 1980 (Box 27)
    - K-98 (24), 1981 (Box 27)
    - K-99 (25), 1981 (Box 27)
    - K-100 (26), 1980 (Box 27)
    - T-10 (11), 1981 (Box 28)
    - T-15 (16), 1981 (Box 28)
  - The Mac Davis Show
    - Final draft, 1976 (Box 28)
  - Mannix
    - "The Blind Mirror", 1969 (Box 28)
    - "Color Her Missing", 1969 (Box 28)
    - "Eight to Five, It's A Miracle", 1967 (Box 28)
    - "A Penny For The Peepshow", 1969 (Box 28)
    - "The Playground", 1969 (Box 28)
    - "The Solid Gold Web", 1969 (Box 28)
    - "The Thirty-Two Friends of Gina Lardelli", 1968 (Box 28)
  - M_A_S_H
    - "Kim" (revised portion only), 1973 (Box 28)
  - Miami Vice
    - Untitled pilot, 1984 (Box 29)
    - "Calderone's Demise", 1984 (Box 29)
    - "Cool Runnin'", 1984 (Box 29)
    - "Heart Of Darkness", 1984 (Box 29)
    - "Hit List", 1984 (Box 29)
    - "Not Necessarily The Swamp Thing", 1984 (Box 29)
    - "One Eyed Jack", 1984 (Box 29)
    - "The Three Eyed Turtle", 1984 (Box 29)
  - Miss Black America Pageant
    - Final draft, 1977 (Box 29)
  - Mission Impossible
    - "Blues", 1971 (Box 30)
    - "Decoy", 1970 (Box 30)
    - "Nicole", 1969 (Box 30)
    - "The Pendulum", 1972 (Box 30)
    - "Run For The Money", 1971 (Box 30)
    - "Ultimatum", 1972 (Box 30)
  - The Mod Squad
    - "The Activist", 1970 (Box 30)
    - "My Name Is Manolete", 1969 (Box 30)
    - "A Place To Run, A Heart To Hide In", 1969 (Box 30)
    - "See The Eagles Dying", 1970 (Box 30)
    - "The Sunday Drivers", 1968 (Box 30)
  - The New Odd Couple
    - "The Cordon Bleus", 1982 (Box 30)
    - "The Cordon Bleus" (revised final draft), 1982 (Box 30)
    - "The Cordon Bleus" (shooting script), 1982 (Box 30)
    - "The Cordon Bleus" (revised shooting script), 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Felix Sings The Cordon Bleus", 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Frances Moves In", 1982 (Box 31)
    - "A Grave For Felix", 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Opening Night", undated (Box 31)
    - "Opening Night" (revised final), 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Opening Night" (final draft), 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Opening Night" (shooting script), 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Opening Night" (revised shooting draft), 1982 (Box 31)
    - "Oscar Dates Felix's Frances", 1983 (Box 31)
  - The Outcasts
    - "The Alligator King", 1968 (Box 31)
    - "The Long Ride", 1967 (Box 31)
    - "They Shall Rise Up", 1968 (Box 31)
    - "The Butcher of Bennington", 1968 (Box 31)
  - Paris
    - "Pay The Two Bucks", 1979 (Box 32)
  - The Powers Of Matthew Star
    - "The Racers Edge", 1982 (Box 32)
    - "The Racers Edge" (revised final draft), 1982 (Box 32)
  - The Quest
    - "The Seminole Negro Indian Scouts", 1976 (Box 32)
  - Roll Out!
    - "Blues For B.J.", 1973 (Box 32)
  - The Rookies
    - "The Code Five Affair", 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Dead Heat", 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Dead, Like A Lost Dream", 1972 (Box 32)
    - "Invitation To A Rumble", 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Journey To Oblivion", 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Journey To Oblivion" (final draft), 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Lamb To The Slaughter", 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Reluctant Hero", 1975 (Box 32)
    - "Shadow Of A Man", 1975 (Box 33)
  - Room 222
    - "Can Nun Be Too Many", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "I Didn't Raise My Girl To Be A Soldier", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "I Didn't Raise My Girl To Be A Soldier" (revised final), 1973 (Box 33)
    - "I've Got The Hammer, If You've Got the Thumb", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "Jason And The Big Mo", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "Love Is A Many Splintered Thing", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "M P G", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "No Island Is An Island", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "No Island Is An Island" (revised final), 1973 (Box 33)
    - "No Island Is An Island" (second final), 1973 (Box 33)
    - "Of Smoke Filled Rooms", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "Pete's Protege", 1973 (Box 33)
    - "Twenty Five Words Or Less", 1973 (Box 33)
  - Roots: The Next Generation
    - Show #1, 1978 (Box 33)
    - Show #1, final draft, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Show #2, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Show #2, shooting script, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Show #4, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Show #4, another copy, 1978 (Box 34)
    - Show #7, 1978 (Box 34)